I and still have a chance of a top eight
finish in the champions league league
phase but they have work to do two wins
will likely be
necessary Barcelona up in second
Barcelona already know that they will be
in the playoffs at least Benfica well
they're chasing a top top eight finish
as well
struggling to get across to that
Carreras with the ball there will a oh
good fer of scored already fire in by
paves that's an unreal start for the
Eagles of Lisbon their first attack of
the game Alvaro Carreras with the
freedom of the left hand side arm in the
air play my way that's the way it came
and look at the runners in the middle
left alone by shelder up he got the call
from pavidis who did the rest it's one-
nil
Benfica that's what Barcelona will do
balde pull back by Rafia for
levandowski balde goes down it's going
to be a corner challenged by Thomas Aro
was it uh a step on the foot yes it was
seeing a lot of those in every game that
we watch at the moment and they're
always painful yeah they are now should
it have been any anything more than a
corner I'm sure it'll be looked
at nothing more to see oh no there is he
is being asked goodness me I thought
he'd set himself for the corner himself
the referee but now he's been given the
uh the flag from V to go and have a look
for himself so Rob deeping thinks it
should be a penalty what is Danny mcy
going to make of it now wow I didn't
think there was enough in this I'm going
to watch it again you can see he quite
clearly knocks the ball around doesn't
he and he does connect with his foot
he's going to give this guy maybe should
have done first time around yeah cuz he
was in a good
position he's not needing much of a look
there we go a penalty for Barcelona away
back into the
game I think it is right I think he does
well he just takes it away from the
defender there and it is that that stamp
on the
foot the perfect man to take the penalty
for
Barcelona and it's more or less the
perfect penalty Benfica won Barcelona
won
and we're only 13 minutes in he's just
so calm isn't he leandi that little
stutter sees where the goalkeeper's
going to go and then he just slots it
home brilliant penalty from
him DOI trying to lay it off and it has
broken here good save from truin to deny
Gabby this might get them excited again
where's chesy going oh it's a real mixup
paves with an open goal Benfica have
their lead
back vanelis pavis and the double
tonight A misjudgment from vek
chzn and he's feeling the pain of it
such a mistake you know he doesn't need
to do that the defender's there the
defender can cover he's made the
decision to come out you've got to clear
it you've got to get to the ball if
that's the
case he's not going to mind though is
he that's
Carreras finding kooku who gets it into
Aus Asus outside of the boot great ball
Chesney out oh is that going to be
another penalty it is one for Benfica
this time Chesney was late I think it's
the right decision guy I think it's a
penalty yeah again this the the ball out
from the back good pressure from Benfica
but look at the spaces that Barcelona
reling lovely ball and you can see just
touches the ball over the top a chzn
little dink over the top of him comes
out catches him penalty for me actor
curu is there
first nobody was getting the ball from
him here vanelis paves 31
benica and he's got himself a
hatrick Benfica fans absolutely
Delirious here didn't even look where
the goalkeeper was wasn't in the
corner chzn goes the opposite Way Slots
at home brilliant Pap pabz what a night
for
him pedri lines up the shot and it's uh
nicely saved by trouin and he makes sure
it doesn't spin
away just opened up nicely for for pedri
but yeah lots of possession for
Barcelona you can see both the WID men
are tucking in and it's the fullbacks
that are trying to to give them the wh
but great opportunity for PF to counter
there oh what's happened goodness me
Barcelona have got a goal out of
nowhere anat
truin it's another huge mistake isn't it
oh wow it's renia's goal how much does
he know about this nothing that's the
weirdest goal I've ever seen scored in
the Champions League yeah me
to Thomas Aro it's a really good ball in
have le this wasn't far from it shielder
up and it's
in Ronald Aro has put the ball into his
own
net
Carreras pedri for Barcelona into the
feet of fan Torres lamin Mal goes down
and the r gives a
penalty he's also giving a yellow card
to otamendi this is not over yet Bar's
second penalty of the
night and it wasn't in doubt the only
thing that is now is Benfica holding on
to get the three points it is 43
just a bit of room here for Ferman he
just got a yard away from Alexander bar
who was indebted to the help of Thomas
Aro barer in a
pedri shifts it Clips it in good ball
and barer a
level you knew the chance would come
absolutely buried Eric Garcia rising to
head in picked out with the perfect
cross into the box oh this is brilliant
from Barcelona it's a short Corner what
a delivery this is just shifts it onto
his right foot just changes that angle
and he gets in between two Defenders
gets up so well and the power is enough
to take it pass to
brilliant played in for Carreras across
comes to Young and he plays it back
against Carreras and then caught him leg
raised High to stop him getting up and
running free kick Benfica and they look
like the team that are going to have the
last chance to win it if they want to
always high line here we here we go Di
Maria round the back otamendi can't get
there this is bar Bar's lift to the
back anonio Silva leaves it for barrero
comes down for barrero as he
fouled Benfica implore the referee to
give a penalty but he's not going to and
Barcelona clear where's the goalkeeper
troid he's gone back to his line it's
Rafia and Rafia has won it for Barcelona
I do not believe it from 42 down to a 54
lead with what looks like being the last
kick of the match this meanwhile is
going to be
checked V are going to have a
look to see whether Benfica ought to
have had a
penalty rafine you're not hanging around
to find out he had support he could have
played it across but I think that's what
Benfica were expecting
so he catches trit and wrong foots the
keeper to make it Benfica four Barcelona
five he's the v he's already called his
colleague Danny mckel over to the screen
once tonight this is
enormous and it's not going to come to
anything there will be no Benfica
penalty there will be no chance for them
to win the game 5'4 because it's
Barcelona who've done
that now instead it's the Benfica bench
the fourth official has called him over
and somebody on there's got a red card
it's not Bruno
lar he took took himself away hands in
prayer yellow card's all over now
benfica's KN Ferman Lopez getting a
booking for getting himself too involved
as well that's kind of
academic and that is it after 8 minutes
of added
time a wild wacky wonderful night in
Rain soak Lisbon and Barcelona somehow
have made it six wins in a row in the
Champions League to make sure of a place
in the last eight in the top eight to
take them through to the last 16 Benfica
had the game one they've lost the game
to brilliant baly
Barcelona Benfica four Barcelona
5 subscribe now to enjoy sports from
across the world